Hello, Namaskar friends, welcome to
our YouTube channel Investment friends, today
we have brought another video with which we are going to
tell you what has been the performance of the stock market today,
what has been the
activity, so in that sense, there has been the
highest rise in the stocks,
okay friends,
and
in the pharma and FMCG sector, there have been the
cities with the highest births, in
which the
market has seen the highest decline,
whose name is friends,
Bajaj Auto Limited, friends, Bajaj Auto
Limited
and if we talk about its returns, then
you are seeing its return today,
on your screen, it has a
high return of 1.255%, so
its high return is 1.55%,
if you have a holding in it, then you
can send your shares and withdraw your profit,
friends, if you
want to invest in it, then right now
is not a good opportunity, friends, do not
invest right now, if you have
invested your money in it, then
you
can withdraw your money because the market today is
moving on you, so the market is moving at 1.41% right now,
we are showing you the live market,
this video is that 28  September,
as we are seeing now,
we are showing you on 28th September at 9:54 in the morning, the
market has just started, in the big one we are
telling you about Bajaj Auto Limited,
which has seen a huge jump of one point
[Music]
it opened from 5000 and at
4647 paise and it is going to
537 and it is still going at two.
So friends, this was our first stock
in the market, now let's go to the next stock which has
given high returns today, so
friends, the second stock in front of you,
friends, its name is
[sangeet],
it is running, so if
you have holdings in this stock, then
you can send your stock
and withdraw your profit, yes,
but you should not invest your money right now
because right now is not a good time to
invest in it, if you have holdings, then
you can withdraw your profit, yes
friends, so this was friends, friends,
in the market of LNT stock, you go to the next stock in
which there is a fraud, that is
Vedanta Limited, friends, Vedanta Limited,
whose share price is running
and its share price has increased by 70 paise, friends,
if you
can create your profile in it, it is a good opportunity to
take your photo, but right now is
not a good time to invest in it, if we
talk about the market performance in it, then its
[sangeet] 5 days ago was
37 percent, what do you say, the
market was doing well, 5 days before that
Talking to friends, even 5 days ago, there has been an
increase in it, that is, there has been an
increase of 1.65%, which means Axis Bank is giving a good amount of money, so
friends, if you are
asked for my suggestion, then you should
maintain holding in it, if in the long term you will get a
good profit in it, that is,
your money will not sink nor will it go to waste,
but your money will make money
and a person is sexy only when he
makes money from money, so
this was friends, another share from our fourth,
we discuss with you, which is
our last share, so
friends, Godrej Consumer Products
Limited, the
return has increased, that is, it has increased by 0.28
percent,
as you can see on their screen, there has been an
increase of ₹5.80 paise,
if friends, you have a holding in it, that is, you have
bought the share, then you
can invest in this share and
withdraw your broadband, so
friends, these were our top 5 shares which are at the
top of the list of tenants,
now let's talk about our
lower cells, so which 5 shares have
declined significantly and there is a good
opportunity in them  We will discuss it in detail,
its name is
it is running.
If we talk about its returns, then
friends, how much has it fallen? As
you can see, it has fallen by 3.22%.
Today, friends, is a good
opportunity to invest in it. You can invest in it,
buy it and
hold it for some time to make your profit.
As soon as there is a fall in it, we will inform you
and will also inform you. For this,
you have to do an important work for us.
You just have to subscribe to our YouTube channel so
that you can
receive notifications of the videos posted by us
and you can get only profit. So
friends, we request you to
subscribe to our YouTube channel
so that you will never
face any financial problem in the future.
Yes, friends,
we promise you that we will not let you face any problem. For this,
subscribe to our YouTube channel. Keep liking and
sharing the video. Let's talk about the big stock.
Friends, you can hold Test Mahendra
Sher Limited
and increase your money.
So friends, let's go
next.  In the big group of shares, which
is the next share in which
you can hold it? Starting with
General Insurance Corporation Limited,
friends,
Insurance Company Limited wants to
sell its shares, but now is a good
opportunity to invest in it. So,
friends, this was our
second-
largest share. Now let's move on to
its name.
If we talk about it,
friends, you
can take your profit by holding it. So, friends, this is
our third-largest share. Now, let's move on to the fourth-
largest share. There has been a decline in it. So, the
fourth number share which we are selling is
Asia
Paints Limited. Friends,
its share price is running at ₹323.
If we talk about it, its return is
₹214. So, your
risk of loss increases because if you
buy shares in small amounts, your
risk reduces by at least
80%.
But there are some shares which we
can trust. In the long term, they are going to be long-term.
Profit is bound to happen, so there is
always a need to be a little patient in it,
but you will not suffer any loss. Yes,
friends, you will not suffer any loss if you take care of the operation.
So you will not suffer any loss,
which we will show you friends,
if we talk about its maximum, then there has been a lot of deception
in this city, as you can see that
in the long term it is going to go up, no matter how much it
falls,
but it will go up
friends, because
you use such things a lot
in the world, which we use every day, it will never go down
and
in the long term its profit is going to be only profit
and inflation is going to increase in it, so
friends, if you invest money in such a city, then
you have to be a little patient,
but you get a good amount of money,
you should see what kind of
things we have which will definitely never end,
if you work hard then you
can easily find out
in which city we should invest money, we should buy them in large quantities
so that we do not have to face a decline, so
friends,
you must be aware of Asia Paints, that
Asia Paints is used in all the houses across the world,
because even if there is a distemper increase, then
all of it is from Asia Paints, and there are no
wedding programs etc. and Diwali is celebrated
in it  So, there is painting, repairing of the house etc., so
friends, Asia Paint is
used, oil, shampoo etc., these too are never going to
end because this
too has a share, friends,
you can invest money in that too and
sometimes we need Colgate etc., it is our daily necessity, so
this is never going to end, so it is
very good to invest money in these companies
and friends, as soon as there is a decline in these companies,
you should always be ready, be
alert, as soon as there
is a decline, you should invest your money and keep it
safe, but whenever there is an increase,
if you have an emergency, you
can withdraw your money and
earn profit, so friends, this is
HDFC Company Limited, talk to the share
and you can withdraw your profit,
we will keep informing you like this and will keep
giving information, for this, like the
video to subscribe to our YouTube channel,
friends, we will meet
in the next video, till then take these Vande Mataram,
Ram Ram to all friends